regator.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Regator - Curated Blog Search and Discovery

Regator respects the personal privacy of visitors to our website and mobile applications (“Regator Service” or "Regator"). Please read this Internet Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand what information we collect through our websites, what we do with that information, and how to safeguard the personal information you provide to us.

## INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY

Your personal privacy is a principal concern to us at Regator. Our goal in outlining our policy on the collection and use of user information is to ensure the highest level of confidentiality and security. When you provide your personal information on any Regator service, we will not give or sell your personal information to any outside company for its use in marketing or solicitation without your permission, which may be express or implied. We will maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and it will be used only to support your user relationship with our service and to assist us in providing better and more targeted services to you. Additionally, internal practices are in place to help protect your privacy by limiting employee access to and use of customer information. When we ask customers/listeners to provide their personal information on a Regator service, it is done with the goal of improving the relationship between Regator and the user. At Regator, we allow our users to maintain control over their personal information while attempting to provide a more interactive online experience. Our intention is to send e-mail only to users who have chosen to receive such e-mails by supplying an email address at time of registration. At any time, you have the right to decline receiving future communications from Regator in any manner, including email, fax, telephone and postal mail.

## HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

When you browse any Regator service, you do so anonymously. Personal information—including your e-mail address—is not collected. However, there are three (3) ways in which Regator may collect information about you.

  1. Regator may request that you voluntarily provide personal information for purposes such as site registration and correspondence. Information that we ask you to provide may include your name and e-mail address. We may also request that you provide user preference information that may be needed to register or subscribe you to services or features.
  2. Like many other commercial websites, Regator may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our website is used. Cookies are small text files on your system used for keeping track of settings or data for a particular website. You may turn them off through your browser or set your browser to notify you before accepting them. Regator uses cookies to store information necessary to remember your recent settings and help accessing the site. Any information that we may store in cookies is used for internal purposes only.
  3. Each time a Regator page is requested from your browser, we log your computer's IP address into our log files. Your computer has been pre-assigned a 12-digit number from your Internet Service Provider and may be static or dynamically assigned—this number is the IP address. Regator uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track movements on the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any other personally identifiable information by Regator.

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect only information that is needed. We limit the collection of information about our users to what we need to know to manage their site membership, to provide customer service, to offer new products and services, and to fulfill any legal and regulatory requirements. We tell our users about the general uses of information we collect about them, and we will provide additional explanation if requested. A user may change, update or add additional information about themselves at any time through their Regator settings.

## SECURITY

Access to user information is limited to those who specifically need it to conduct their business responsibilities. We use security techniques designed to protect our user information—especially information that is used by employees and business partners to fulfill user services. In addition to providing users with the opportunity to refuse marketing offers, we release information only at the users' requests, or when required to do so by law or other regulatory authority. When a court order or subpoena requires us to release information, we notify the user directly so that his/her legal rights can be exercised, if appropriate. The only exceptions to this policy are when we are prohibited by court order or law from notifying the listener/customer, or cases in which fraud and/or criminal activity is suspected. Finally, each Regator employee is personally responsible for maintaining user confidentiality. All Regator employees are required to sign an agreement that they will comply with these policies. Employees who violate these policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination of employment. Employees are expected to report violations—and may do so confidentially—to their managers or other supervisors.

## USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

As a result of providing your personal information to us, Regator can provide a more customized online experience, making your interaction with us more productive, helpful and fun, and will enhance the services our service can bring to you. If you provide us with your e-mail address, or have done so in the past, we may send you occasional e-mail notices. Your information or email address is never sold to a third party At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these communications from us by simply replying to the e-mail address included in every e-mail message that you receive from Regator.

We do monitor URL click-throughs found in our email messages, Facebook messages and Twitter tweets originating from the service . The click-through rate is reviewed in order to track (i) post/topic popularity and/or user interests. Individual activity is never shared with employees or third parties.

## PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. Regator Services are not directed at children under the age of 13 and we will not knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personal identifying information. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any information about yourself to any Regator service. http://disney.com may be a more suitable destination.

## OTHER DISCLOSURES

Third-party Internet sites, including all blogs featured on Regator and services accessible through Regator Services have separate privacy and information collection practices, independent of us. Regator has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we aim to protect your personal information, Regator cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

While Regator puts forth its best efforts in adhering to these minimum privacy standards, additional restrictions may be imposed to comply with state and local laws.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

The Internet is an evolving medium. If we need to change this Internet Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes to this Internet Privacy Policy on this website and update the reference to the effective date to reflect the date of the amendment. By visiting a Regator Service you agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Internet Privacy Policy.

Revised April 14, 2010.
